<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Fallout - Vault 14</name> <!-- Name in mod list -->
  <packageId>Nolabritt.FalloutVaults</packageId> <!-- author.modName --> 
  <author>nolabritt</author>
  <!--
  <url>
  -Text Hyperlink-
  </url>
  -->
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.2</li><li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  
   <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Twink.Vaultfurniture</packageId>
      <displayName>Vault-Tec - Handy things for your vault!</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/818773962</steamWorkshopUrl>	
	</li>
  </modDependencies>
 
 
  <loadAfter>    
  <li>Twink.Vaultfurniture</li>
  </loadAfter>
 
  
  <description>
Lore:
Since the great war, there have been many rumors of a Vault-Tech Vault that has been lost to time, the illusive Vault 14. While the whereabouts of the vault remain a mystery, there are still elements of the old world floating around that may hold clues to its location… 

Content:
This mod adds Vault-14 to the game. 
Vault-14 is an autogenerated, fully furnished Vault that offers your colony the chance for adventure, exploration, and riches. 
The journey to and through the Vault is filled with danger and will be a very long endeavor; so, make sure your team is well prepared.
The Vault is filled with items that can be deconstructed or claimed for use in your colony. Likewise, the Vault itself can be used as new location for your colony. 
The Vault’s power grid and central lighting systems are offline after all this time; however, the power grid can be reenergized to assist in the exploration of the vault. The central lighting system can be reactivated by using the Overseer’s terminal. 

Instructions: 
After activating the mod, a Pre-war Vault-Tech Satellite will crash on your main colony map. The satellite can be used inside of a Vault-Tech Transponder to locate Vault 14. The transponder can be built after researching Vault-Tech Production Techniques. Once used, the transponder will open a new map near the colony that contains the entrance to Vault 14 inside of a mountain cave. To open the vault, you must have a colonist near the vault entrance. Opening the vault will make a new map under the entrance that contains the vault. It is very dark inside the vault, but upon reaching the overseer’s office, you can hack the Overseer’s Terminal to reactivate the lighting. 


</description>

</ModMetaData>